const contest_3_2 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The so-called batteries used in mobile phones are dry voltaic cells. What type of cells are they?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Secondary Voltaic Cells - (they can be recharged after they have been discharged)",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electrochemistry", "Voltaic Cells"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Consider the reversible reaction:\n$$\n\\mathrm{A}_{(\\mathrm{g})}+3 \\mathrm{~B}_{(\\mathrm{g})}+\\text { heat } \\rightleftharpoons \\mathrm{C}_{(\\mathrm{g})}+\\mathrm{D}_{(\\mathrm{g})}\n$$\nAt which of the following temperatures will the equilibrium constant be largest, $200^{\\circ} \\mathrm{C}$ or $300^{\\circ} \\mathrm{C}$ or $400^{\\circ} \\mathrm{C}$ ?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$400^{\\circ} \\mathrm{C} . \\quad$ (Le Chatelier's Principle)",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Chemical Equilibrium", "Le Chatelier's Principle"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Give the colour that a copper compound imparts to a colourless flame.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Green",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Flame Test", "Copper Compounds"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The impedance of an ac circuit is $75 \\Omega$ at the frequency of a signal applied across the circuit. Find the rms voltage across the circuit if the rms current in it is $0.40 \\mathrm{~A}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$30 \\mathrm{~V}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["AC Circuits", "Impedance"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A $2 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object moving at $15 \\mathrm{~m} \\mathrm{~s}^{-1}$ collides head-on with and becomes attached to a stationary $1 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object. Find the common speed of the objects after the collision.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$10 \\mathrm{~ms}^{-1}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Mechanics", "Collisions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The bob of a simple pendulum which has a length of $2.0 \\mathrm{~m}$ and a bob of mass $0.8 \\mathrm{~kg}$ swings to an extreme position that is $0.25 \\mathrm{~m}$ above its lowest position. Find the kinetic energy of the pendulum when it returns to its lowest position.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$2 J$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Mechanics", "Pendulum"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "How do nastic movements differ from tropic movements?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Nastic movements differ from tropic movements in that the direction of tropic responses depends on the direction of the stimulus, whereas the direction of nastic movements is independent of the stimulus's position.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Plant Biology", "Movement"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which of the chambers of the mammalian heart possesses the thickest wall?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "The left ventricle",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Human Biology", "Cardiovascular System"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Blood grouping in human beings is derived from combinations of how many alleles?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Three (3)",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Genetics", "Blood Grouping"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the equation of the tangent to the curve $y^{2}=4 x$ at the point $A(1,-2)$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$y=-x-1$, or $x+y+1=0$\n[ $2 \\mathrm{ydy} / \\mathrm{dx}=4, \\mathrm{dy} / \\mathrm{dx}=2 / y, m=2 /-2=-1, y+2=-1(x-1), y=-x-1$ ]",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Calculus", "Tangents"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Solve for $x$ given $(1 / 25)^{x+2}=125^{x-2}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x=2 / 5$\n$\\left[5^{2(x+2)}=5^{3(x-2)},-2 x-4=3 x-6,5 x=2, x=2 / 5\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Exponential Equations"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "If $(2 x+3) /\\left(x^{2}-x-6\\right)=A /(x-3)+B(x+2)$, find the value of $(A+B)$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "2\n$[2 x+3=A(x+2)+B(x-3)$, for $x=3,9=5 A, A=9 / 5$, for $x=-2,-1=-$\n$5 B, B=1 / 5$\n$A+B=9 / 5+1 / 5=2]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Partial Fractions"]
    }
]
export default contest_3_2